Does 8CG have the potential to increase
sensitivity and increase ejaculate
volume at 500 IUs a week?
Have the potential? Yes, that dose in my
in as far as I can recall has not been
studied. So that might be too low of a
dose. The the doses that have been
studied is 250 to 500 every other day
when you're talking about with
injectable testosterone.
>> Yeah. If you're talking about hCG alone
or hCG with anything other than
injectable, I I don't know the answer
because it really hasn't been studied.
But the minimum dose I think that's
studied that we have good confidence
that works is 250 every other day. So
I'd be concerned about 500 working. But
that being said, I have there are
anecdotal examples I have of guys using
like a thousand a week and they still
have sperm counts. But I want to be very
careful because you know having four or
five patients like that doesn't mean is
not as good as like a research study
with like you know
hundreds of patients.